acapela.tv 2010-06-11

# acapela.tv : be content

## Privacy

If you're reading this, it's because you want to know what information we, Acapela Group, are collecting on www.acapela.tv, what we're doing with it, and what your options are. If you have any questions or concerns after reading this, please email using our contact form.

This Privacy Policy applies to the Acapela.tv website located at www.acapela.tv ("Site"). This notice describes only our online information collection and use practices at this Site; it doesn't apply to information we collect about you offline (such as over the phone) or in different situations (such as through email correspondence).

This privacy policy is effective as of November 1, 2008. In the future, our Site or our practices may change, and if appropriate, we will revise this Privacy Policy to reflect the changes. We'll post the updated version here, and we'll notify you if we think the changes will significantly impact the treatment of information you have already provided.

## Information We Collect

Information You Provide: You provide certain personally identifiable information (such as your name and email address) to Acapela Group when choosing to participate in various activities on the Site such as chat, posting messages in the games comment section or in our forums, sending feedback, entering contests, responding to surveys, or subscribing to newsletters or other mailing lists. 

You may choose to disclose information about yourself in our online chat rooms, forums, game comments or in creating user "profiles". Information that you disclose in these areas is public information, and will be accessible to anyone who uses our Site. However, you may choose to have your profile page be public or private. In the case where you chose to make your profile page private, the information there will only be visible to you.

Other Information We Track: This Site uses passive tracking technologies to log non-identifiable information such as IP address, browser type and Site usage (for example: what pages are accessed, how often, referring/exit pages and URLs). We may also employ "cookies" or similar technologies that provide additional functionality to the Site and help us analyze Site usage more accurately. You can set your browser to reject cookies, but if you do, some features on our Site will not function normally.

Invite a Friend: You may invite friends to join the Acapela.tv community by using the "invite a friend" feature. You will be required to submit your name and email address, as well as their name and email address. Your friend's personal information that you submit in this feature will be used only to send the email you request, and will not be stored or maintained by Acapela Group.

## How We Use This Information

We use the information we collect to respond to your requests and provide customer service, to remit revenue share payments, process credit card payments, let you know about new games and other news from Acapela.tv, ask for your input and feedback on what we are doing, provide personalized services and recommendations, and as may otherwise be described in this Privacy Policy or at the time that we collect information from you.

We use both your personally identifiable information and certain non-personally identifiable site usage data to improve the quality and design of the Site and to create new features, promotions, and services by storing, tracking, and analyzing user preferences and trends.

We may also combine the information you submit to us with information we have collected from you in other forums, such as through emails or offline, or with publicly available information or information we obtain from third parties.

## When We Might Disclose Information

As part of our regular business conduct, we may share information with companies or individuals providing services or acting on our behalf, such as companies providing technological or fulfillment services. In the event that there is a change of corporate ownership, the new owners will of course be provided with our files, including information you have submitted. We will also share information with government officials, including law enforcement officials or court authorities, in order to cooperate with a legitimate investigation.

Unless we tell you first (such as at the time we collect information from you), or unless it is part of a specific program or feature in which you have elected to participate, we do not share personally identifiable information that we have collected (such as name or email address) with other, third-party companies for their own commercial or marketing purposes.

## Links and Third Parties

From time to time we may include at the Site links to other websites as a service to you. The third party sites are operated by companies that are outside of our control, and your activities at those sites will be governed by the policies and practices of those third parties. We encourage you to review the privacy practices of these third parties before disclosing any personally identifiable information, as we are not responsible for the privacy practices of those sites.

We sometimes work with third parties to add features or advertisements to our Site. These third parties may place cookies on your browser when you visit certain pages of our Site, or collect cookies that they have previously placed, along with the URL of the page you visited. We do not control those third parties or their use of data. In some cases we may provide tools for you to limit data sent to third parties. This privacy policy does not cover those third parties’ use of data.

## Security

We use standard and reasonable technological and procedural measures to protect the information you provide. We urge you to protect your password by not sharing it with anyone else, and to take measures to prevent it from unauthorized access or disclosure. For example, select number and letter combinations that would be difficult for a third party (or hacking program) to determine, and do not write down your password next to your computer. 

## Your Options

If you are receiving Acapela.tv email advertisements and no longer wish to receive those email messages, you may opt out at the time you receive the message by following the instructions in that email. Please allow ten days for your request to be processed.

If you do not agree with the privacy practices described in this Privacy Policy, it may be best to limit your level of interaction with our Site, which could include simply not providing us with personal information. While this will limit the services that our Site is able to provide (chat, friends lists, challenges, etc.), most of the games will remain playable. This option may be best for those who do not wish to provide the mandatory information required to set up an account.

For questions or concerns regarding the use of personal information you submit to us, please use our contact form.
